ahahahahahaha
ahahahahaha
Ahahahahahaha
Just me?
ahahahahahaha
ahahahahaha
You're so cool.
She's a good girl, really.
Hello, I'm Hina Okamoto from Nogizaka46
Today, I'm with the Fukai Ito group of Sakurazaka 3rd term students.
We're going to spend an hour or so together.
I haven't been able to meet up with Ito's group yet, so
I'm going to go to my room first and wait for Ito's group.
We haven't been able to see each other recently.
I'm glad to see them after a long time.
I'm still alone.
I wonder where I should sit.
I don't know.
Well then...
Here.
I guess here.
I don't know.
Thank you for watching.
One.
What shall I do? There are so many things I want to do.
I really don't know what to do.
I have so many toys.
Wait.
I'm so happy.
I have a lumen gas.
I love Lymegas.
I love it.
Ljumgath.
I'm so happy.
I'll keep it nearby.
I'm Tanami Mukai from Sakurazaka 46! I am Tanami Mukai of Sakurazaka46
From now on.
I'd like to go to Okamoto Hina-san's room.
Let's go!
I'm not the type to get nervous.
But...
Going to someone's room...
I'm nervous.
Which is it?
I'll get out of your way.
Congratulations!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Excuse me.
Have you been sitting here in a while?
I've been sitting here.
Well, let's start with the board box.
How's that?
From the boardroom, then.
Oh, shit.
What do we do?
You gave me an hour.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God, we're gonna have so much fun.
What do I do?
It's grown.
But the fat might be different.
What do you think? I'll just say it's not the same height.
I have a cut here.
I'm sorry, it was cut.
I was just making it up as I went along.
I'm getting a little pin prick.
I got a pinch.
Is it an angle? I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know.
I think we're being a little oblique, aren't we?
They're just being random.
Do you know what we're doing?
I didn't ask.
Look, there.
Is that what I think it is?
There was a toy.
And I found some helium gas in here.
I've been trying to get it to work.
One time I couldn't keep my voice down.
Oh, I'm sucking on it.
There you go.
I'm sucking on it.
What do you mean now? I'm just getting started.
No, it's not.
No, really.
I've always had a dog voice.
I can't change it.
Well, if you had another bottle, would you try it?
Hey, I got some crackers or something.
I'm scared.
You should've given him some bread or something.
No, this one's better.
This one's different?
I don't know.
Let me ask you something.
Let's give it a try.
Let's try it.
Ping.
Let's suck together and make funny noises.
I'm gonna pinch your nose.
How are you going to suck it in if you're pinching your nose?
If you pinch your nose, you won't be able to suck.
How did you do that? How did you do it?
You got it!
Ready?
Suck it.
How do you smoke?
Oh...
Oh, it stopped.
But it stopped.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no!
It's no good.
Wow, there are so many cameras.
Yeah.
So I was looking for a square, because I couldn't go to the square even if I wanted to, you know.
Why are you looking for squares?
Where to turn.
I was looking for squares, you know.
I thought, “Where can't I hide?
Where are you pointing the camera?
Here... I wanted to surprise the thread at first.
That's true.
Yes, but it was taken from that side.
I knew it was made in such a way that there are no squares.
That's for sure.
It's amazing.
It's cool.
Isn't it just right?
Did you see that?
It's not appropriate.
I was caught.
It's always appropriate.
Please say “stop.
Here we go.
Let's go!
Stop. STOP
Rundown Fun Shopping
Mamimneme in your bag
Mamimnemo
It's wrong, isn't it?
Mamimnemo, right?
It's wrong.
Let's not do this.
Poison is poison, but what kind of poison makes shoppers happy?
Poison?
Poison.
You mean “sorry”?
It's something like that, isn't it?
Like the eye of the potato or something?
It doesn't please me.
What pleases you?
Poison.
Poison is great.
The birds are chirping.
I love it.
I don't know.
Oh, my God, how is that possible?
Where's the answer?
Oh, my gosh!
What? Sorry!
That's what I'm talking about!
What kind of ball disappears when you touch it?
Soap bubbles!
Is that what you mean?
I feel so accomplished!
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
I feel like maybe I'm getting better.
I was such a messed up kid.
A messed up kid?Messed up kids?
A fucked-up kid.
What kind of kid were you?
I remember helping my mom clean up.
You know, vacuuming, like, all the time, you know, the rooms.
I thought I'd do that for you.
I was trying to help her clean up.
So I spread detergent all over the house.
Liquid ingredients like this.
That's how I did it.
That's how he did it.
I'm scared.
I know, it's scary.
Can you forgive him? When they do that to you.
But I love you.
She was able to hold it together.
Yeah, she was a mess.
I was a messed-up kid, too.
I guess.
Oh. Oh.
Hmm.
You see this edge of the TV?
There's lip balm nicely on this rim.
That's nice.
She's a princess!
There's a TV set, isn't there?
I broke my TV recently.
What?
It's not that I broke it, it's that I broke it.
What? All of them.
The TV broke.
I thought maybe it was clogged with dust.
So I took it all apart.
You know, piece by piece, you take it all off.
I vacuumed everything out.
There were grooves.
So, you know, I thought I wanted to crunch it up. So, you know, I wanted to crunch it.
I know it's probably clogged with dust.
I thought I'd do some crunching.
I thought maybe I could crunch it like this.
But I don't have a nail gun.
I have a substitute. A pasta boiler.
You know what I mean? You know, the kind that's crunchy?
That's, uh, that's how I did it.
A lot of it went down.
It just kept going in and out.
I was thinking, “Oh, no.
I thought I got most of the dust out.
The TV didn't come on.
I knew it wouldn't work.
And there are too many screws!
Where are the screws?
I was thinking, “Where are the screws?
It's really cool that you took the TV apart.
It's so cool that you took the TV apart.
He's a good boy.
He's cute.
That's the first time anyone's ever said that to me.
Okay, what's next?
I'm going to buy something...
Purchases?
I didn't buy anything.
Wow, you scared me.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What's this?
I've got something I want to do.
There's something that hasn't been bothering me lately.
What's that?
You know what it is? Do you know what it is to be human?
I don't know.
And it's a game where we have to move around a lot to get it, and there's definitely a right answer.
Are you sure? Really?
I've been trying for a long time, but I just can't do it, so I thought I'd clear this up today.
Okay, I'll do it.
Okay, I'll go through here like this.
Then, you squat with your legs.
Then, I'll go through here, right?
What do you think? What do you think?
And then, right?
And then, this.
Itoha-san went through here,
What, here?
Here.
Through here.
And then..,
And then, oh my...
Then, you do this.
And then..,
entsche
Let's do something different next time.
Sorry, we're starting with the same thing now.
Together?
Just now.
I've never seen you look so awkward.
That's the first time I've ever seen you look awkward afterwards.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm going back.
Can you think of something for me to do with this?
I'm sorry.
It's a foot-press.
Same as before.
That's great.
I don't remember this.
I've been with you the whole time.
Let's do something crazy.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
When this happens...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
This is Butt Tall.
It's a butt tall.
So Ito can pull this out of Hina's tall.
Hina can pull out Ito's tall.
Wait!
Wait a minute.
Can I pull it out?
Okay.
Hold on.
I think we made it.
I thought it was a historic moment.
I know you gulped.
It took our breath away, didn't it?
It's really fun.
It's like a school day.
School?
What is it?
School.
What's that?
School dismissal.
What's “after school”?
School's out.
What is “after school” time?
The time between school and school time.
Like a five-minute break.
That's right.
I've never heard of it before.
What?
Didn't you say 5 minutes of school, 30 minutes of school?
Like the big break.
What?
Lunch break and recess. Lunch break big break
School's letting out for a bit, but it's not stopping.
It didn't stop.
Oh, my God!
Where are you?
Hiroshima Prefecture.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I'm sorry.
Uh...
It's at the bottom.
Bottom or halfway down.
Oh, so it's down.
Okay.
That's so awkward.
I'm comfortable with it.
What's wrong with the picture over there?
Down there.
Like that one in Yamaguchi.
I'm sorry... there's no Japanese or anything.
The dunes...
Sand dunes?
Tottori Sand Dunes... and some friends.
What do you call them?
You mean, like, near Okinawa?
That's right.
More like Okinawa.
Let's try this.
Let's do this.
The one who opens the door has 10 minutes afra.
Yes, of course.
Ah!
There it is.
I'm nervous.
I'm so nervous. Oh, I'm scared.
Oh, I'm scared.
Aww.
Uh-oh.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha.
Eh, I'll take Erlich.
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Oh, my God!
Koi, you're so scary!
I'm so scared!
It's so scary!
It's stuck deep in?
It's stuck.
It's like glass...
Aaaaah!
Why did you just...
You mean it went all the way in?
You scared the shit out of me.
That's disgusting.
Wait a minute, there's a makeup artist here.
There's a make-up artist here.
That's so sweet.
It's so cute when it rises in your eyes.
I, Izawa, fixed it.
Fixed what?
Izawa's definitely playing with my hair.
What do you mean, black?
Wait a minute.
It's so boring!
You mean black beard?
That guy...
He cut his face a little bit.
Oh, my God!
That's new.
Tell me what's new about it.
I think I can go outside now, so I'm going. I'm going to go now because it looks like I can go outside.
I'm gonna go now. I'm gonna go now. I'm gonna go now.
What are you gonna do? Go outside.
We're on foot again, aren't we?
I'm more excited to go outside.
What more do you want?
I'm out of here.
Don't talk about yourself.
How's it going?
Wow!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Mmm! Yum!
It's so cute!
And this one too!
Oh, man!
Wait! Wait!
Wait!
Thank you for watching!